http://www.stageagent.com/pages/privacy

Join StageAgent today and unlock amazing theatre resources and opportunities.
StageAgent Distance Learning Hub
Teaching or learning remotely? Here are some of our favorite resources to help maximize theatre e-learning and enjoyment.
DISTANCE LEARNING HUB
Participate
Find:
Background
Estage Enterprises, inc DBA “StageAgent” is a company that specializes in the creation, marketing, and delivery of high quality theatre education content and social networking tools. StageAgent runs the websites WWW.STAGEAGENT.COM and WWW.STAGEAGENT.ORG (collectively, the “Sites”).
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before accessing materials or registering on the Sites. By visiting or using the Sites, you accept and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, do not use the Sites. Unless otherwise indicated, these Terms are applicable to all of the Sites. Please also review our website Terms, which also governs your use of the Sites along with any agreements entered into between you and StageAgent pertaining to your use of the Sites.
The Information We Collect and Use
StageAgent collects personal data that you voluntarily provide to us when you register for an account on the Sites or sign up for our e-newsletter. Personal data may contain your name, email, image, phone number, location along with other information you provide.
StageAgent collects billing information when processing membership payments.
StageAgent logs your visits and use of the Websites such as when you view or click on content, or ads or perform a search. We use log-ins, cookies, web beacons, device information and internet protocol (“IP”) addresses to identify you, your location, and log your use.
StageAgent collects and stores data about you when you use our messaging platform to communicate with other users.
StageAgent may also obtain information about you through third party sources as permitted by applicable law, such as public databases, social media platforms, and marketing partners.
Information you post in social community environments offered on the Sites as well as other interactive features in which you may provide us with your submissions. If you provide personally identifiable information when you use any of these features, that personal information shall be posted on the Sites. You are responsible for your communications, and are responsible for the consequences of their posting.
In HTML e-mails that we may send you, we may use technical methods for a number of purposes, including determining whether you have opened or forwarded those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e- mails. These technical methods may enable us to collect and use information in a form that is personally identifiable.
Use of Cookies
We use “cookies,” a small text file transferred to your device, along with similar technologies (e.g., internet tag technologies, web beacons, embedded scripts) to help provide you a better, more personalized user experience. These technologies are used to:
Make the user experience more efficient
Remember your preferences (e.g., browsing language, account login information)
Help us understand and improve how visitors use our website, including which of our pages and products are viewed most frequently.
The Options/Settings section of most internet browsers will tell you how to manage the cookies and other technologies that may be transferred to your device, including how to disable such technologies. You can disable our cookies or all cookies through your browser settings. Users may also opt out of the NAI's interest-based advertising network by clicking here and following the on-screen instructions. Please be advised that disabling cookies may impact many of our websites’ features.
Information obtained by third parties:
To support and enhance the Sites, we work with a variety of third party marketing analytics service providers and website analysis firms, such as Google and Facebook (collectively, “Third Party Service Providers”). These Third Party Service Providers collect and use non-personally identifiable information, such as your mobile device ID, about your visits to and use of the Website, as well as other websites in order to serve you with content tailored to meet your preferences and likely interests. Aggregate demographic and interest data will also be used for market research purposes.
We use Google Analytics which is a web analytics tool that helps us understand how users engage with the Website. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track user interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how users use our site. This information is used to compile reports and to help us improve our Website. The reports disclose website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Personally Identifiable Information from Children
StageAgent does not solicit personal information directly from children less than sixteen years of age nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children less than sixteen years of age who may visit our Sites. Any information sent to us regarding children is given by parents, guardians or teachers and serves the purpose outlined on our Sites.
The StageAgent.com website is intended for use only by individuals aged 16 years or older. However, StageAgent.org, known as "StageAgent for Schools", may offer services to users under the age of 16 under the supervision of the user’s academic institution. In such circumstances, the student’s academic institution has been instructed to not input or reveal any personally identifiable information of the student.
If you are a parent or guardian or teacher and believe that your child or student has provided StageAgent with personally identifiable information, you should notify us at privacy@stageagent.com so that we may immediately delete the information from our servers.
Examples of How StageAgent Uses Your Data
To create an account for you to access content and services on our Sites.
To personalize content to give you a better experience, such as sending you targeted job postings or performance announcements based on your location.
To respond to your requests or to manage user accounts.
To receive product feedback and understand our users better in order to improve StageAgent.
To monitor the safety and security of StageAgent's services.
To use data and content about users for communications promoting membership, job posting, and engagement with StageAgent, on StageAgent properties and across other platforms.
To target and measure the performance of advertisements displayed to our users directly by StageAgent or through third party advertising partners, on and off StageAgent.
Third Party Content and Linked Sites
Third parties provide some of the Content on our Sites such as audition and performance notices. StageAgent makes no representations or warranties as to the completeness, accuracy, adequacy, currency or reliability of any content supplied by third parties and will not be liable for any lack of the foregoing or for any errors or omissions in any content supplied by third parties. In addition, third parties may offer goods, services and other materials to you on the Sites. Such dealings are solely between you and the third party. StageAgent will not be responsible for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings. StageAgent makes no warranty concerning, is not responsible for and does not endorse any third party provided goods or services, and you agree that any recourse for dissatisfaction or problems with those goods or services will be sought from the third party provider and not from StageAgent.
Descriptions of, or references to products, services or publications within the Sites do not imply endorsement by StageAgent of that product, service or publication. The Sites may include links to other sites that are not maintained by StageAgent. Websites of those third parties are subject to terms and conditions different from those found here and it is your responsibility to ensure that you have read and understood them. StageAgent is not responsible for the content of those sites, does not endorse those sites, and makes no representations whatsoever concerning the content or accuracy of such other sites. If you decide to access any third party site linked to the Sites, you do so entirely at your own risk, and you may be exposed to offensive, indecent or objectionable content. StageAgent shall have no liability for any loss or damage arising from your use of any such sites.
How StageAgent Shares Your Data
StageAgent shares your personal data with third parties only when it is necessary to offer the services offered on the Sites, legally required, or permitted by you.
StageAgent will not use any personally identifiable information to advertise or market third party services to its users, and does not sell or rent such information. We do use the information you provide to us to improve our offerings and to provide you with the best possible experience on our Sites. We may share the IP address that we automatically collect with various third parties.
We use YouTube's API services in connection with our service to provide certain features. As such, you acknowledge and agree that by using our Sites, you are also bound by Google's Privacy Policy. In addition to the rights set forth in Section 2, you may manage your YouTube API data by visiting Google's security settings page at https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions.
We may also share your personally identifiable information with law enforcement officials, or other third parties, when we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order, or similar legal procedure. In addition, we may share personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that the disclosure of such information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, to investigate violations of our Terms and Conditions or to the extent necessary to meet national security requirements. If we sell or otherwise transfer part or all of our business or assets to another organization, such as in the course of an acquisition, merger, bankruptcy or liquidation, we may transfer your personally identifiable information. In such an event, we will endeavor to require the buyer or transferee to agree to our commitments provided in this Privacy Policy.
StageAgent shall ensure that a contract is in place between it and any third party entity or agent that participates in an onward transfer of personal data from the Sites. The contracts specify that such personal data may only be processed for limited and specified purposes consistent with the consent provided by the individual and that the recipient will provide the same level of protection as stated in the Principles.
Talent Profile
If you register for an account on StageAgent.com, your talent profile may be publicly discoverable across the world wide web. You may modify the information on your talent profile at any time by logging into your StageAgent account.
Teacher Profile
If you register for an account on StageAgent.org as a teacher, your profile may be publicly discoverable across the world wide web. You may modify the information on your profile at any time by logging into your StageAgent account.
Messaging
Users on StageAgent.com may share information with other users by sending and receiving messages on the StageAgent messaging system. When you send email or message StageAgent customer support, StageAgent will collect and store your name, email address and the content of your message so we can provide customer support.
Posting Jobs and Performance Announcements
When a user posts an event such as a job, audition or performance announcement, the notice may contain personally identifiable information. By posting these notices on StageAgent, you consent to share the contents of the casting notice with other StageAgent users, as well as make the contents of your casting notice publicly discoverable across the world wide web.
Other Parties Designated by You
When using the StageAgent Service, you may share your data with other parties designated by you. For example, when inviting a StageAgent user to apply to your casting notice, you may also share personally identifiable information with that user.
Service Providers
From time to time, we may partner with unaffiliated companies or individuals for market research, product development, quality assurance testing, or similar purposes. These companies or individuals may be provided with access to personally identifiable information, but we will require by contract that they agree to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of such information. We also may subcontract with other companies and individuals to do work on our behalf; they may be provided with access to personally identifiable information, but only as needed to perform their functions.
Data Processors
StageAgent, as a data controller, collects and shares data with different data processors in the following categories:
Technology and Infrastructure: StageAgent distributes data to processors in order to host, enable and support the StageAgent platform and service.
Analytics and Reporting: StageAgent distributes data to analytics platforms to better understand user behavior and track key business metrics, in order to provide a better service to its users.
Marketing Partners: StageAgent distributes data to marketing companies to facilitate email marketing, on-site promotions, and social media, search, and display advertising campaigns.
International Data Transfers: Information, including information collected in the European Economic Area ("EEA") may be transferred, stored and processed by StageAgent and its services providers in the United States and other countries whose data protection laws may be different than the laws of your country. We will protect your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Notice wherever it is processed and take appropriate steps to protect the information in accordance with applicable laws.
California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 entitles residents of the State of California to request from a business, with whom that resident has an established business relationship, certain information regarding the types of personal data the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. If you would like to request a copy of this information disclosure from StageAgent, please contact us at privacy@stageagent.com.
How does StageAgent protect information you provide to us?
We have implemented and maintain information technology security measures designed to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorized disclosure to or access by a third party. Your account and associated information is protected by a password, which you should keep secret at all times. We encrypt password information stored in our databases. Although we make concerted efforts to protect personally identifiable information and maintain security, it is not 100% guaranteed. Outages, attacks, unauthorized use, or other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.
Data Ownership
StageAgent retains a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, sublicensable and transferable right to use, publish, display, modify and copy User Provided Content in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, and any other agreement you have entered into with StageAgent. If a StageAgent.org account owner has granted access to Authorised Users via their account management portal, the account owner shall have the right to access and use any data submitted by the Authorised Users.
Newsletters
StageAgent may offer e-mail newsletters to people who register on the Sites and other persons who opt-in to our newsletter. By registering for an account on our Sites, you may receive occasional emails about your account, blog articles or about updates to the platform. You may unsubscribe from these emails at any time.
Accounts provided to you as part of a School or District License.
If you were granted an account on StageAgent.org that was provided to you by your academic institution, then your account may be managed by a school or district administrator who may have access to all of your account information including – but not limited to – all your presentations and reports. In addition, your school or district administrator may be able to:
Change your password.
Suspend or terminate access to your account.
View statistics regarding the use of your account.
Access, delete or copy your presentations and reports and any other information stored as part of your account.
Based on the license terms agreed between the academic institution and StageAgent, StageAgent.org account holders may be allowed to grant a limited number of Authorised Users access to StageAgent content and materials. These Authorised Users will access the Site via 6-digit access codes provided by the account holder. Authorised Users will not need to register for accounts with StageAgent.
How you can access, change, or delete personally identifiable information?
You can contact us to access, change, or remove any personally identifiable information that we have collected from you by sending an e-mail to privacy@stageagent.com. Please include your full name, e-mail address, and Site accessed so that we can better assist you with your inquiry or request. Please be advised that: (i) requesting the removal of or not providing personally identifiable information may result in the termination, removal, or blocking of your account, registration, or access to the Sites; and (ii) changing personally identifiable information may affect your use of the Sites including the correctness of any results. Once you request a change or removal of your personally identifiable information or your account, we can give you no assurances that such information or account may be retrieved or reopened in the future.
Note that If you choose to delete your account on WWW.STAGEAGENT.ORG, the information associated with your account along with Authorized Users you have added will be deleted.
Will there be changes to our Privacy Policy?
We expect to amend our Privacy Policy from time to time as we change the registration procedure, possibly introduce or alter our offerings, change levels of user participation, or release new features. In the event of material changes, StageAgent will provide notice by means that are reasonable under the circumstances, such as by posting a notice on the Sites. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept those changes. Please review this Privacy Policy on a regular basis as your use of the Sites will be governed by the then-current Privacy Policy.
StageAgent retains the right in its sole discretion to remove or delete, temporarily or permanently, any and all information, including personally-identifiable and non-personally identifiable profile and registration information, Submissions, and any other information collected from or provided by you. Please note that, at all times, you should update your personal information to provide us with current e-mail addresses.
Severability:
If any provision of this Privacy Policy is deemed invalid, unlawful, void, or unenforceable by a court or arbitrator of competent jurisdiction, then that provision shall be severed from this Privacy Policy, and the invalidity of the provision will not affect the validity or enforceability of the remainder of this Privacy Policy.
How to contact us:
You can contact us with any questions by sending an email to privacy@stageagent.com or at the following address:
Chief Privacy Officer: Jason Engleman
327 Fuller Street
Redwood City, CA 94063
Last updated on February 1, 2019.
×
Oops! This page is only accessible by StageAgent Pro members.
Take your performing arts career to the next level
Gain full access to show guides, character breakdowns, auditions, monologues and more!
UPGRADE TO PRO!
or log in to your account
Close
You need a Pro account to access this feature.
×
Take your performing arts career to the next level
Gain full access to show guides, character breakdowns, auditions, monologues and more!
UPGRADE TO PRO
SIGN UP
or or log in to your account
